♪La la la la la la, la la la la la la♪
♪La la la la la la la la la♪
♪No matter what day it is,
I'll spend it with you♪
♪We're more sure
of each other than ever♪
=Watching Heart Signal with You=
(Before recording starts)
I feel like the couch got softer.
Let's see.
(Feeling it)
I really wanna look at
those photos taken here.
Is this the second one?
No, not the first or second one.
The third? Second?
This was your last one,
right?
Let's see.
Just a quick look.
Everyone's seated?
Tea first.
Thanks.
Cui Kaiyi, don't do that.
Those are the hands that save lives.
Don't use them for this.
Leave the dirty work to us.
Dirty work.
Remember back then?
Tea.
During the first part of that dinner.
Thanks.
This glass always
plays such an important role.
Exactly.
Whenever things get awkward...
Tactical...
Tactical sip of water.
If it's something you don't
wanna watch, just drink.
Especially if you can't bear to watch.
How've you been lately?
Happy.
Happy every day.
I ship them online.
I get to ship Everlasting YiHeng
in person.
Front-row shipping.
With both of them here,
I can really go all out now.
We get the full experience.
Right.
Oh no. I feel so reserved this episode.
Why'd you put on so much blush today?
So reserved.
(Reserved)
Today, Liang Renfang and I
are gonna take you guys on.
Rival lane.
I ship YuLiang Never Fades too.
YuLiang Never Fades. That's right.
YuLiang Never Fades.
YangShizi.
So,
does Yu Yang talk about Fang
every day back at the dorm?
Yeah.
He showed me one of his drawings.
It looked like it was covered
in little squares.
I was really curious.
When I first saw it,
I actually doubted him.
I said, "Did you really draw this?"
"No secret expert helping you?"
She thought you were his secret artist.
So, were you?
Did you help at all?
He did it all himself.
Really?
He even showed it off to me afterward.
What was the drawing of?
I thought you'd helped him.
What was it, roughly?
It was a scene from the dinner.
Oh my God.
He added captions too,
plus portraits of him and me.
That's so thoughtful of Yu Yang.
I heard someone spotted you
in public, right?
Yeah.
I even dressed up for it.
I was worried no one
would take my picture.
Just kidding.
Terrified no one would take one.
Hahaha.
Why aren't my candid pics online yet?
Let's start
with introductions.
Let's do it.
Hi everyone, I'm Cao Yiheng
(Cao Yiheng)
from Heart Signal 9.
Hi everyone, I'm Cui Kaiyi
(Cui Kaiyi)
from Heart Signal 9.
Hi everyone, I'm Liang Renfang
(Liang Renfang)
from Heart Signal 9.
I'm Chen Hewen
(Chen Hewen)
from Heart Signal 9.
Welcome, everyone.
This is my first time
doing a watch-along
with Cao Yiheng and Fang.
But it's my second time with Cui Kaiyi.
Right.
Last time, I told Chen Hewen
about Three Star Mound.
Right.
And "three outfits".
"Three outfits".
And now we're back at it.
Are you curious?
Very. Super curious.
I heard you were
at the amusement park that day.
Yep.
Okay, let's look forward to it.
I'm ready. Let's watch.
This is...
This is us.
I remember that wind chime.
Straight into a date.
(Smiles)
What are you smiling at?
You're both wearing green.
Flowers again?
Yeah.
Which bouquet is this now?
Let's count.
One on our first date.
One on Children's Day.
Then when you took me to my exam,
you brought one when you picked me up.
Yeah.
So this is the fourth.
Oh my God.
Perfect score.
(Pulls out her chair)
Give it to me.
Here's your gift.
Yeah.
I'll hold the flowers.
(Exchange gifts)
We both have so much stuff.
Are you exchanging gifts?
Yeah.
Put it here.
Can I see the gift?
(Smiles)
(Opens the gift)
It's a camera?
(Can't stop smiling)
She can't hide that smile.
I'm trying not to smile.
(Surprised)
How'd you know I wanted one?
Wasn't it obvious?
How was it obvious?
I want to buy an instant camera.
(Heard it)
Here!
(Instant camera)
I remember during your last watch-along,
you guys mentioned
how Meng's camera made you want one.
Yeah.
Then
the comments were like,
"Cao Yiheng, buy her one."
Buy it.
He did.
Bought it right away.
A fragrance, right?
Aromatherapy.
Didn't you say
you don't sleep very well?
For sleep.
Sleep aromatherapy.
Do you like it?
If it's from you...
(I'll like anything you give me)
I'll sleep with this scent
every night now.
(More than just a scent,
it's company every night)
So you'll think of me, right?
You two...
How is this any different
from actually dating?
I can't watch anymore.
Sorry, guys.
We're being cheesy again.
So sweet. Really sweet.
I went home and deleted
all my romance dramas and novels.
I remember when I brought
this aromatherapy back,
I put it by my bed.
Then I asked those two,
"Can everyone smell it?"
They both said yes.
So I used two drops the first night
when I went to sleep.
Does it actually help you sleep?
It does.
It even helped Yu Yang.
No wonder everyone
in your dorm sleeps so well.
The aromatherapy scored big.
We can make different styles.
We can make several.
Yeah.
(Smells)
Which one do you like? Let me guess.
This is the one
you couldn't smell earlier.
I think I'm getting a cold.
It's okay.
(Takes off his jacket)
What a man.
A real man.
(A true gentleman)
You're a real gentleman.
That was next-level.
So thoughtful.
I think a lot of the things
that really win girls over
are the little things.
Those effortless little details.
Yeah. Honestly, I'm
not that attentive.
Just being honest.
I can't do what Cao Yiheng does.
I'm probably just
not that detail-oriented.
Learning on the spot?
Yeah. I'm really learning.
Learn from the master.
When it comes to the little things,
I think Cao Yiheng really is...
our role model.
Our role model?
You're seriously...
Are you really our role model?
I'm alright.
From now on, I'll take it off
no matter the weather.
I think you guys
have different perks.
This bracelet's so pretty.
When it comes to style,
(Praising)
you're the expert.
I match them to my mood.
Guess you're in a good mood today.
Oh my gosh.
These two are so busy.
They catch me off guard every time.
Even when they're busy,
they still find time to flirt.
One out of every three lines
is flirting.
Yep.
Here he comes.
Your King of Sweet Talk,
Cao Yiheng, is back.
With a whole basket of sweet talk.
So how many times
a week should we meet?
You're already talking
about how often to meet each week?
They're discussing
how many times a week to meet.
What do we two talk about every day?
Are we living on the same timeline?
How'd you get this far already?
Did you two know each other before this?
No.
If we did, neither of us would've come.
You still had to come.
Otherwise, I wouldn't learn anything.
Maybe three times.
(Glances)
What do you think?
Do you think that's too little?
Not really.
We're not that far apart anyway.
Yeah, it actually feels pretty close.
What about what we agreed on last time?
Video calls every day?
You two...
How'd we get here now?
What day...
What year is it again?
They're already video calling.
Wait, how did
meeting several times a week
turn into video calls every day?
It's like you two
already went out there,
started living your life together,
then came back here.
This timeline doesn't add up.
Go ahead.
I just can't keep it in.
Seriously, that's exactly it.
You're even worse
at hiding things than me.
I just wanted to ask.
Yeah.
Because later on,
long distance
will definitely be an issue.
Even though Tianjin
to Beijing is pretty close.
But we still
can't be together every day.
So I think
it's about how we make things work.
One thing is how we communicate.
The other is the distance.
So we want to talk it through
beforehand.
That just reminded me.
About being independent.
They
exposed Cao Yiheng.
He's not independent at all.
Not at all.
Only in front of us.
He's independent around us.
If you had to choose again,
what color would you pick?
Still green?
I'd still pick green.
Because
if I'd picked another color,
maybe
things would've been different.
What if we never met, right?
Everything happens for a reason.
Even back when I was
in the Green Space,
they actually asked me
to send a text
and choose another room.
But I didn't send one.
I just left it up to fate.
Let someone choose you.
Yeah.
Then I have a question.
If green wasn't an option,
what would your second choice be?
I'd go to yellow.
Yellow?
Who said you could go to yellow?
Yellow Space
is already packed.
I'd fit in perfectly.
Okay.
This is a must.
That depends on how busy you are.
If you're upset, I'm not busy.
(If you're upset, I'm not busy)
Then he'll be upset every day.
I'm getting shy. I can't watch anymore.
But I don't think he's ever been upset.
I've never seen him upset.
But I don't want you to feel pressured.
Even though we said
we'd video call every day,
if you're ever too tired,
and don't feel like calling,
or just want to rest,
that's totally fine.
I think I'd
want to call every day.
Me too. Right now,
I'm seriously shipping them.
(If you're too tired, after I call you)
I wish you two call each other every day.
That might cheer me up.
I'll livestream our daily calls
for everyone.
You two have to call every day now.
Because sometimes,
I get pretty stressed,
and I need someone to support me.
Got it.
He got the message.
We know who wears the pants now.
So concise.
Respect.
Yeah.
Just do whatever...
I made it crystal clear.
Message received.
Don't you say "got it"
to everyone who texts you?
That's my first time
saying it out loud.
Got it.
Mm-hmm.
Cui Kaiyi, I really think
you're so brave.
You know, I
honestly think
with Yu Yang,
back then, I couldn't say
even one
flirty line like that.
You know?
I really think you're so brave.
No.
Everyone moves at their own pace.
Yeah. As long as you're
on the same wavelength, it's right.
You put it on.
(Made by Cao Yiheng)
Back then, I used
the red one as
(So pretty)
a red bean.
A red bean.
It's seriously so pretty.
So this is where all the details were.
The Signal House is kind of
a dreamy place.
Does it feel unreal?
Like, when you think about the future,
is there anything
you're worried about?
Anything at all?
Watching you two now,
I can't see anything to worry about.
Seriously, nothing at all.
Just steady happiness.
I'm getting shy.
I can't even watch this anymore.
Don't be scared.
You're usually so bold.
Why are you suddenly so scared?
Oh my gosh.
I only get scared
with people I'm close to.
With people you're close to...
How is this any different
from a confession?
You two...
Confessing every day.
Did you expect me to say that?
Not at all.
I was wondering why you were scared.
I wondered if I'd done something
that made you feel insecure.
But that's not it.
I think everyone probably feels
like the house is...
I mean, everyone here
is completely genuine.
But the place itself still feels
kind of dreamy.
And the way we are together,
I don't know if it'll still be the same
in real life.
Because here, we can put aside...
Yeah.
Everything else and just spend each day
completely free of that.
It's so intense.
Yeah.
You spend so much time
together.
And it's all sweet.
Yeah.
Everything feels perfect.
And I asked you that
because sometimes, with people
I'm close to,
I can get a little oblivious.
Like when we first meet,
I might talk more,
and I'll notice
the little things about you
and really listen when you talk.
But once we get close,
I tend to talk less.
So I'm scared I'll get too comfortable
and miss what
the other person is feeling.
Because when Cao Yiheng gets upset,
he tends to handle it himself.
I'm scared if he keeps doing that,
it'll affect
his feelings and our relationship.
It's okay.
We'll try to talk things out.
I honestly didn't notice it
about Cao Yiheng at first.
But later on,
I realized he's really thoughtful.
- Super thoughtful.
- Yeah.
And he's also the kind of person
who knows how
to support you emotionally.
Seriously.
He'll never leave you hanging.
Not once.
And his
eyes are always on you.
It's always like...
Cao Yiheng always looks like...
Watch the TV.
I am. I'm watching.
Okay, let's keep watching.
If anything's bothering you,
just tell me.
Got it.
Got what?
Nothing else to say? "Got it", huh?
I literally just said you
never leave people hanging.
We usually eat at home.
My dad's a pretty good cook.
Both my parents cook really well.
I need to play this part for my parents.
I'll send it to them.
My parents watch every episode.
They'll be so happy when they see this.
Gotta give them credit.
Wait
till you come over to my place
and try it.
Why do you two always...
Oh, so that's why...
Sorry.
This is too...
At this rate, you're already
at the meeting-the-parents stage.
I was wondering why
there was this disconnect.
Turns out the disconnect is you two.
You two completely
cut the rest of us out.
Once this airs, we'll have to go.
First it's video calls every day,
then it's
"come home with me for dinner"?
What's with this pace?
Wait till you come to my place.
You guys didn't say stuff like this?
Way too fast. Not at all.
I really just say
whatever comes to mind.
His eyes went wide.
I was pretty happy then. It was just...
I felt really welcomed.
Welcomed?
Yeah.
And I was already thinking
about how I'd...
how I'd get there.
Like, should you
take the subway
or the train?
And what you'd wear, right?
Yeah.
Mentally preparing
myself.
You were already
getting ready for that day.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Nice.
We spent forever doing crafts here.
How did we talk about so much?
It's fine.
Show more. I wanna see it.
It's all good stuff.
Yeah.
Is it good?
(Cao Yiheng)
Of course the dish you picked is good.
You nailed my taste.
(Compliments)
(Cui Kaiyi)
You've got something...
You're eating,
and I'm watching you.
Something black,
on the left side of your hair.
(Helping)
What is that?
The "rom-com" is back.
So by this point,
(Fell off)
you were already getting handsy?
What do you mean, handsy? I wasn't.
That's already...
I was just being helpful.
He had something on him,
so I took it off.
Nice. I'm shipping you.
You match the whole room.
We're both in green today.
It feels like
(Wore green last time)
we're on his home turf.
(It's really different this time)
Yeah, green.
But the second time,
even though I still sat in the corner,
I actually wanted to sit there.
You came right over.
I remember.
Because I remember you saying...
if the other person's passive,
you'll take the lead.
If they take the lead,
you'll pull back a little.
Yeah.
Can't let you make the first move.
So did you really think
that if, on day three,
at our second dinner,
I hadn't come over to you,
we would've missed our chance?
I wouldn't say missed our chance.
But
I think I might've disappointed you.
No, I wasn't disappointed.
Because that never happened.
What kind of relationship dynamic
do you like?
What kind do I like?
I'll give you an example.
What do you wanna do right now?
Zone out.
Then let's zone out.
So cute.
What do you wanna do right now?
Do what I love with someone I like.
Two space cadets.
(Two dummies)
Two little bunnies.
When did you draw
those two bunnies in the study?
We did draw one.
I forgot when.
I forgot too.
We were in the study every day.
It was on that blackboard.
That study basically became your room.
You might as well just move in.
It's basically their
newlywed suite.
Yeah.
What are you saying?
Someone bolder than me showed up today.
Just wait.
We're about to see YuLiang Never Fades.
The view behind us is so pretty.
(It's like a comic)
It's seriously gorgeous.
Seriously.
So beautiful.
It's so pretty.
Guess the person you see the view with
matters more.
(The person you see
the view with matters more)
Here we go again.
See? This is what I mean.
I got all this from you.
Blame me.
So he had a master coaching him.
That's why whenever I say,
how are you so smooth?
he says it's all because of you.
And I'm like, when did I teach you?
I actually really like
weather this extreme.
Being on the road with you
in weather like this,
out here,
driving.
I like it too.
It feels like we're
escaping the apocalypse.
(Like we're escaping the apocalypse)
Yeah.
You remember everything you said.
Seriously. That's exactly how it felt.
Thunder kept going
"boom, boom" ahead of us,
and the sky was so dark.
Were we on the highway or...
The overpass.
Right.
There were barely any cars around us.
Lightning stretched
as far as we could see.
And behind us was this gorgeous sky.
The sunset.
You eloped.
It felt like escaping the apocalypse.
Like eloping.
I declare that right then,
you two were already together.
Congratulations to the happy couple.
Congratulations.
You could've just
left the show right then.
No need to stay for the rest.
Just stop participating.
Just become professional shippers.
Professional shippers.
Keep watching.
Doomsday Elopement.
Why was I sitting sideways
the whole time?
Because you wanted to be closer to him.
Oh my God.
I really was sitting sideways
the whole time.
I feel like you're more...
You think about more things.
Like...
Didn't I say earlier
that you're really open and confident?
But you actually think a lot
about everything.
You think things through really well.
I just feel like you're really
reliable
and you make me feel really safe.
Yeah.
Reliable.
Yeah, with the two of us,
you'd guide me,
and we'd get to know each other
on a deeper level.
But I think
it goes both ways.
We guide each other.
Yeah, so it's not just me guiding you.
It's more about us doing it together.
Without you,
it'd be completely different.
We're on the same wavelength.
(Beijing Happy Valley)
Whose turn is it?
Handsome.
So handsome.
Pretty.
Pretty. So pretty.
Oh my God.
Love this.
(Smiles)
(Waves)
(Waves back)
So pretty.
You look so good with your hair up,
Fang.
(Hello)
You look great with your hair up.
Yeah, it gives a totally different vibe.
Yeah.
Another foil perm day.
Looks good.
(Compliments)
So relaxed.
Let's go.
Your foot...
Why do you have a bag?
(Bandaged injured toe)
(Open Day)
Bandaged injured toe.
Why don't I get you a wheelchair?
Yu Yang already feels bad.
I'm really fine.
(It's okay)
You need one.
I'll get you one.
You can sit.
Thank you.
We've unlocked...
(Opens the footrest)
A new mode.
A whole new mode.
Yu Yang saw me wearing heels again,
and my foot was hurt again,
so he said he'd get me a wheelchair.
It's pretty bad.
Even if you wore flats,
it'd still...
Flats hurt even more.
Yeah.
Because flats press against your foot...
And rub against it.
Yeah, because the bandage
covers the toenail,
so flats just don't work.
But it felt
really...
really different.
Of course.
That day at the amusement park.
It kind of felt like
what we'd be like when we're old.
When you're old?
It was just
really sweet.
(Happy Valley)
Are either of you afraid of heights?
I love rides like these.
I think he is a little afraid.
But that day, just to go with me,
he faced his fear.
Brave for love.
When was the last time
you came to Happy Valley?
I came before I started college.
I remember...
It's been long for me too.
we'd come here
on school trips as kids.
So neither of you
has been there in ages.
Yeah, it's been a while
if Yu Yang went there
on school trips as a kid.
Yeah, if it was when he was a kid,
then that must've been...
20 years ago.
That's brutal.
Pretty much.
Carousel.
Then
let's play rock-paper-scissors.
Pick one. You first.
I'll pick that one.
(Fang: Roller coaster)
Let's do it.
- You pick this one.
- Okay.
You went straight for the craziest one.
(Yu Yang: Carousel)
Rock-paper-scissors.
You won. Let's do that ride.
Let's go.
He looks
uncomfortable.
I'm getting nervous.
Now I'm nervous too.
(Smile slowly fades)
That smile vanished instantly.
This is terrifying.
Look at Yu Yang's eyes.
The light's already gone.
He can't open his eyes.
(Scared)
(Glances)
It's honestly pretty scary.
Closing your eyes helps.
(Grabs on)
(Holds on tight)
(Smiles)
You two with all this touching, I...
So we're only talking
about them, not you now?
We weren't talking about you.
How does it feel?
I'm sweating.
You're sweating?
Play that again. Come on.
Replay it ten times for me.
Play that move ten times.
(Smiles)
Yu Yang's eyes opened right up.
(Holds on tight)
Yu Yang, you were just scared.
What's going on?
Yu Yang couldn't wait to hold hands.
Yu Yang's like,
give me the wildest ride.
Even though I was scared too,
I wanted to say it's okay.
Yu Yang's like,
the second you held my hand,
I was all in.
All in.
If I have to fly, I'll fly!
Yeah, spin me as many times as you want.
Yu Yang's using every bit of courage.
(Nervous)
And his eyes still closed.
I really didn't close mine.
My eyes were open the whole time.
So brave. That's amazing.
I got the full experience.
I mainly wanted to see his face.
(A sweet burden)
(Eyes closed)
I feel like Yu Yang
(Joking)
aged ten years up there.
Help!
Yu Yang's done.
You had me start
with something this intense.
Big sigh of relief.
Oh my God.
That's hilarious.
Alright.
I'm not scared of anything now.
(Not scared anymore)
The Courageous.
There you go. He's The Courageous now.
You know his hair
was totally "blown up" afterward?
You know?
Good thing that day he specifically
got that foil perm.
It was already all fluffy.
Then we got on,
and when we got off...
It looked like he had
a whole new hairstyle.
Like he had a bird's nest on his head.
That's too good.
Still handsome though.
I actually like this hairstyle on him.
It looks good.
This is more my speed.
Finally, Yu Yang's favorite part.
(Relaxed)
Finally, a ride he likes.
Now we're finally doing
YuLiang Never Fades.
Here we go.
He's completely different
(Smiles)
from how he was on day one.
Yeah.
He's opening up more
and more.
Yu Yang, I don't know you anymore.
At the amusement park,
I felt even more sure about my feelings.
It felt like we got closer and knew
each other better.
Grew a little closer.
And I feel like
on the roller coaster,
I became a little braver too.
That's why I
reached out and held his hand.
For one, I think it was
a brave way to express myself.
And second, I was worried
he'd be scared.
So I wanted
to reassure him.
It feels like we now share
this memory together.
It was a really unforgettable date.
I'll change, then let's go eat.
(Nightingale Theater)
Nightingale...
Theater.
She changed.
(Please sit)
That outfit's so pretty.
Give me a second.
I'm guessing he's getting a gift, right?
(Leaves)
Here comes the gift.
I got you some flowers.
(Thanks)
Flowers.
(I didn't prepare anything)
These are so pretty.
Let me see this.
There's a card too.
(Fang's observation notes)
Observation notes?
Observation notes.
This is the best part.
Flip through it.
I wanna see this.
Let's look together.
When we entered the house...
During introductions,
(I brought some snacks)
you said you don't eat spicy food.
I didn't tell you.
Here we go again.
They were actually for you.
I ship it.
That's basically a confession.
I remember that day.
I even asked,
"Who bought these?"
He said he did.
And I said,
"They're all light snacks."
Then he quietly said,
"Don't you like these?"
I was just too nervous then.
I didn't dare respond.
He thought I didn't hear him.
But I heard every word.
You heard it.
Oh my God.
He drew a picture for every one.
They're really good too.
So I thought someone coached him.
The moment you got up
and walked toward me,
I thought, I'm done for.
I'm done for.
I couldn't see anyone else.
You should've asked
to switch seats with me.
We could've worked something out.
Worked something out?
Easy.
When did he draw these?
He said he drew them late at night.
But he's always the first one asleep.
Fake sleeping.
Fake sleeping?
Fake sleeping!
He waited till you
and Cui Yihang fell asleep,
then he snuck out to draw.
He's always the first one to shower.
Then he lies down right after.
He gets you two to sleep,
then sneaks back out.
He tucked you two in first.
Couldn't let you two copy him.
When did you draw these?
I drew them yesterday.
Let's see.
Here.
(2AM)
(4AM)
For Fang,
who needs sleep anyway?
Oh my God.
(6AM)
Six in the morning.
That late?
(Fang's observation notes)
He even rode the roller coaster with me.
I'm so mean.
No, he was happy.
We've actually known each other for...
over ten days now.
Yeah.
And over these ten-plus days,
there were some
little moments I really treasured.
So I wrote them down.
Wait.
You were touched.
Seriously.
Even I got emotional seeing it.
Because he's always been...
Thank you.
He's not really the type who...
Says things.
Who says things.
Right.
But I'm probably
not someone who's very...
direct either.
I'm not great
at boldly saying how I feel.
And he's afraid moving
too fast would throw off my pace.
Then we'd be out of sync.
So he uses drawings and writing to...
Turns out, all those little details...
He noticed them all.
Yeah. I really didn't
expect that that day.
I realized he's actually
really thoughtful.
Yeah.
You two are so sweet.
You two are both thinking
you don't want
the other person to feel pressured.
And you don't want
each other to feel nervous.
The best pace is whatever
feels right for you two.
Yeah.
I was really touched when I saw it.
Especially because you can tell Yu Yang
has such a rich inner world.
Like when he wrote about
the first night's dinner.
He couldn't see anyone else anymore.
That line really got me.
At first I was thinking,
he even drew pictures?
I really didn't expect that. And then,
he even wrote down all his thoughts.
And his handwriting...
It looked like the letters were dancing.
Yeah.
I thought you two
moved pretty fast at first.
I didn't expect it
to keep moving this fast.
Everyone says it's fast,
but it still feels steady.
Every step has been there.
Yeah.
Because you knew
who you liked from the start,
every step brought you
closer to each other.
So you just kept getting closer.
That got me so emotional.
Okay, let's keep watching.
It's a new day.
Why are you playing in an apron?
What are you two doing?
You definitely weren't back yet.
You two wouldn't play by yourselves
after we got back.
Fang's here.
Hello.
That tone at the end.
All black today, sir.
Yep.
Whenever he says hello or "I'm back",
he sounds like a radio announcer.
You know?
All black today, sir.
(Yep)
He's actually been waiting forever.
(Misses the pocket)
The second I got back...
You lost focus?
What are you doing?
You really had to call him out?
He got distracted.
(Go on)
Okay, Fang's back. Game over.
Have you eaten?
So smooth.
(Compliments)
Did you eat?
Didn't have time.
(I bought brown sugar)
Fang, your eye makeup
(We can make brown sugar ginger tea)
is so pretty.
I was serving that day.
It looks so good.
I remember Yu Yang kept
casually looking over at me
and checking me out.
What's different today?
That's hilarious.
Here we go.
Honestly, Yu Yang's hair
(Okay)
looks different every day.
(Glances)
The glasses make a difference too.
At first, in the house,
I liked his silver-rimmed glasses.
The silver ones.
Yeah, those silver frames.
I remember.
The ones from the beginning.
But everyone online was like,
"Take them off and toss them."
"Never wear those again."
They said the black frames look better.
But whenever he wears the black ones,
he looks so artsy to me.
He's already artsy.
That's just a fact.
Whichever pair Fang likes
is the best-looking one.
Smooth talker.
You two, seriously.
So smooth.
(Yu Yang makes ginger tea for Fang)
What's that?
(Slices ginger)
Brown sugar ginger tea.
(Juliennes ginger)
Very attractive.
Major points.
Look.
(Taste test)
Cui looks great
with this hairstyle too.
Cui, for sure.
(Picking)
See if you can bite through it.
I've never seen Cui like this.
Right? What were we even doing?
Never saw it. Never noticed.
What's going on?
Those two are always so low-key.
You know?
Yeah, super low-key.
Quietly off being happy together.
Are you all totally different
back in the dorm?
He's actually pretty obvious
in the dorm.
Whenever he's texting,
he's secretly grinning.
Secretly grinning.
Oh my God.
The three of you
in that dorm are seriously
absolutely killing it.
Killing it.
(Opens the envelope)
Dear Sun Bohan,
sorry for the messy handwriting.
I had to write this lying down.
Funny enough,
the day before I came to the house,
I went to see Dear You.
Like you said in your letter,
it feels like we've known
each other forever.
I feel the same way.
That date we didn't get
to go on last time,
we'll definitely make it up next time.
Oh, right.
The flowers are beautiful.
Every morning when I open my eyes,
I get to see them.
Thank you
for giving me someone else
besides Si
in this city.
I need another tissue.
I can't take it anymore.
This...
You're crying over someone else's
love story.
Oh my God.
Seriously.
And words are just so powerful.
They really are.
This...
If they play it again, I'm gonna cry.
My tears are seriously about to fall.
You can really feel it.
After spending time with Sun Bohan,
you can really tell
what he was like before Xing came.
Xing really changed him a lot.
Yeah. She made him braver.
Seeing Sun Bohan like this now,
we're genuinely
so happy for him.
And relieved.
Yeah.
What are you two doing?
Doing dishes.
The Haier Brothers, dishwashing edition.
Sha Yue'er, what are you doing?
What's going on here?
What are you doing?
(Glances)
I'm so sleepy today.
What are those two doing?
Doing dishes.
Why am I...
What's with you, Cui Kaiyi?
Fan.
That look...
What are they
doing over there?
Like, what are those two doing?
Why aren't they coming to my Yue'er?
What are they doing?
Doing dishes.
I'll dig this out. Hold on.
Okay.
Why aren't you there?
Do I need to?
Sha Yue'er thought,
I'm staying out of your dishwashing.
Okay.
Okay, once this one's done...
(That should be about it)
He's gone.
(Okay)
What's he doing?
Okay.
(Okay)
He's heading out first.
It's all yours, Zhao Xilun.
(Leave it to me)
Zhao Xilun's like,
I'm washing these by myself now?
I'm out. I'm off to romance.
Oh my God.
It's all a scheme.
I used a little strategy to trap Zhao Xilun.
What's going on?
No, seriously.
(Sha Yue'er)
Why do they always just miss each other?
Mm.
Everyone keeps saying,
"Why do they always
just miss each other?"
Every time it feels
like you're almost there,
and then suddenly...
Because I remember,
on Chill Day,
we kind of just missed
each other then too.
Yeah.
Yeah, you did.
And after that, because
we didn't get a mutual date,
we even had a fight.
Well, not really a fight.
To me, it was more like
a disagreement, plus some...
Misunderstandings.
Yeah, misunderstandings.
So for those two days,
we were both
stubborn.
Stubborn?
Did you want to talk to Sha Yue'er then?
At the time, I just thought,
why is this so hard?
So awkward.
You really wanted to talk first,
but you also didn't want
to make the first move.
You wanted to talk to her.
There were too many people
around at the time.
Now both of them are just lost
in their own thoughts.
Why haven't they come talk to me?
What do I do?
Who's gonna speak first?
I'm not speaking first.
I'm not saying anything.
Whoever wants to can speak first.
Cui Kaiyi doesn't want to talk anymore.
Totally different styles.
Yeah, very different.
Wait, what are we doing here?
This is good. I love it.
No, what even is this scene?
You left Zhao Xilun washing dishes alone,
and you're not even doing
what you came for.
No, why?
What were you thinking then?
What do you even want?
You were definitely looking
for a chance to talk.
(Observes)
(Thinking)
You're really analyzing everything.
Not bad.
Want a picture together?
Sure.
I'm good either way.
(Moves closer first)
Looks like Zhao Xilun got in the shot.
Cui Kaiyi!
You're such a good wingwoman.
Let's see.
We'll shoot from here.
We'll stand here and shoot
for the corner pocket.
Okay, five balls each.
Whoever sinks more wins. How's that?
Okay.
The loser...
does twenty push-ups...
Let's do squats.
Let's bet on who's gonna win.
I'm betting on Zhao Xilun.
Then I'll bet on Sha Yue'er.
Never mind. Sha Yue'er
doesn't look like she'll win.
You don't think Sha Yue'er can win.
I'll go first then, okay?
Okay.
(Sinks the first shot perfectly)
Nice.
Whoa.
The pressure's really on Zhao Xilun now.
Two out of five.
(Chen Hewen: Two out of five)
(One)
Sha Yue'er hasn't made any.
(Last shot)
(Sha Yue'er: Zero out of five)
Zero out of five.
I think she made the last one.
I remember.
(Sha Yue'er: One out of five)
He's looking pretty confident.
No way he goes zero for five.
Five... probably zero out of five.
Feeling it?
Yeah.
(Zero out of four, last shot)
(Two out of five)
Just toss it.
(Zhao Xilun: Zero out of five,
casually tosses it)
Bank it into the side pocket.
(Zero out of five, loses)
Bank it into the corner.
Wait, what are you doing?
(Doing push-ups under the table)
He just wanted to show off his push-ups!
He's been waiting for this.
This guy.
Come buy some bread!
(Fang brought everyone bread)
Are you handing out bread?
This one. I want this.
Little bread shop.
Want anything else?
That's enough.
It's enough.
I'll pack it up for you in a sec.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm so sleepy.
Let's find somewhere to sit.
Where do you wanna go?
Anywhere. Just somewhere with seats.
Sun Bohan was probably
in the study earlier.
(Leaves)
He's making eating bread look so sad.
Ignore the "bad pic".
Oh my God.
If you're playing by yourself,
I'm heading upstairs.
(I didn't beat you last time)
Why are you playing pool again?
I really like playing pool.
It's pretty fun.
(So good)
So accurate.
(Nice shot)
She's really good.
Nice shot.
(Looking at the photo)
(Photo with Sha Yue'er)
Actually, like this...
Looking at this photo now,
I thought it came out pretty good.
It really did.
I remember seeing it then.
It looked good.
Master, give me some pointers.
She's talking to you.
You're still looking at the photo.
Sorry.
I really was...
Give me some pointers.
Looks like your mind wasn't on the game.
I...
(Don't go anywhere. The next episode
is even more romantic.)